A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, President, William M. Dietel papers, RG 2, Series 1 FA774
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, President, William M. Dietel papers, RG 2, Series 1
1962-1987
1975-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund.
Dietel, William M.
FA774
31.6 Cubic Feet 69 document boxes and 1 record storage box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Loosely alphabetical.
Biographical / Historical
William M. Dietel served as the fifth President of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, succeeding Dana S. Creel in 1975, and serving through 1987.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
RBF donated the collection to RAC in 2012. The Dietel papers were transferred to RAC beginning in 1988.
Scope and Contents
The Dietel papers primarily contain correspondence, reports, program planning and evaluation materials and Board of Directors/Board of Trustees records documenting his tenure as RBF President, as well as other professional memberships, positions, organizations and activities he was concurrently involved with. The collection also contains a small selection of personal and semi-personal correspondence.
Other Finding Aids
For other Rockefeller Brothers Fund finding aids please see:
Rockefeller Brothers Fund records
Rockefeller Brothers Fund.; Dietel, William M.
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, President, William M. Dietel papers, 1962-1987; 1975-1987; 1
  - Agriculture - International Agriculture, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture - Meeting of Officers of Foundations concerned with Food, Agriculture, Education and Development, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Development Council - Casebook, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Public Radio, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Public Radio, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
  - American Public Radio Associates, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - American Public Radio Associates, Inc. - Minutes of Meetings, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - American Public Radio Associates, Inc. - Minutes of Meetings, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - American Public Radio - Nominating Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Benedict Foundation for Independent Schools, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - British Institute, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Center for Community Change, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Center for Policy Research, Inc. - The Endangered Sector - Nielson, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Board of Trustees, 1980-1987 (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Board of Trustees, 1980-1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Carter's Grove, 1973-1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Development Committee, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Educational Programs and Policies Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Educational Programs and Policies Committee, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Executives Group Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Executive and Finance Committees, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Nominating Committee, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Governmental Concerns, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Co-operation North, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Council on Foundations - Professional Development Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Council on Foundations - Professional Development Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Creedy, David L. - The STA Schooners, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Dana Hall School Corporators, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Emma Willard Capital Campaign - Weekly Reports, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Emma Willard Fund for Leadership, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Emma Willard School, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 34A)
  - Emma Willard School, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Foundation Executives Group (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Gamwell, Chris - Essay on Values (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Grants to Talented Individuals, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Good Hope School - Board of Trustees, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Good Hope School - Frederiksted, St. Croix, 1974-1982 (Box 11, Folder 40-41)
  - RBF Grant Reports to the Trustees, 1977-1985 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Groton School, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Hampshire College, 1970-1985 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Hampshire College - National Advisory Council, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Harper Woodward Foundation, Inc., 1970-1980 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Heritage Trust, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Heritage Trust, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Individual Giving Project, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Interchurch Center, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - International Philanthropy, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Ireland Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - King Faisal Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Lieng Van Nguyen, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Lingnan College, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Longwood College - Meeting, 1982 September (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Miller, J. Irwin, 1962-1968 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous - A-H (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous - A-H (Box 15, Folder 59-60)
  - Miscellaneous - I-N (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous - O-R (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous - S-Z (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - NAIS - Recruiting Young Teachers, 1982-1986 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - National Business Council - ERA, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Preservation Committee, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Executive Brief, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Pocantico Planning Project, 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Pocantico Planning Project, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 69-70)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - The Nature Conservancy - Galapagos Campaign, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - New York Public Library, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - New York Public Library, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 76-79)
  - New York Public Library, 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - New York Public Library - Confidential Letter - Couper to Salomon, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - New York Public Library - Trustee Campaign Planning Committee (William M. Dietel and Steve Stamos, Co-Chairman), 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - New York Public Library - Long-Range Planning Committee Progress Report, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - New York Public Library - Deaccessioning, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - New York Public Library - Memorandum on Space and Relocation of Collections and Services, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - New York Public Library - Search Committee, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 86)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2020.
  - New York Public Library, 1976-1982 (Box 21, Folder 87-90)
  - New York Public Library, 1976-1982 (Box 22, Folder 91-92)
  - New York Public Library - Capital Needs AD HOC Committee, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - New York Public Library - Budgets, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - New York Public Library - Budgets and Budget Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 95)
  - New York Public Library - Board of Trustees, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 96)
  - New York Public Library - Executive Committee (Box 23, Folder 97)
  - New York Public Library - Board of Trustees, 1986 October 2 (Box 24, Folder 98)
    - New York Public Library - Board of Trustees, 1986 October 2; Audio cassette (Box 2016:FA774:001)
      Researchers interested in accessing this item must request an access surrogate be made. Access to original item(s) is restricted.
  - New York Public Library - Finance Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - New York Public Library - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 100-101)
  - New York Public Library - Nominating Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - New York Public Library - Planning and Resources Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - New York Public Library - Planning and Resources Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - New York Public Library - Research Libraries Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1971-1985 (Box 26, Folder 106)
  - Pittsburgh Foundation, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 107)
  - Pocantico Advisory Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 108)
  - Peggy Dulany - Pocantico Institute Project, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 109)
  - Pocantico Institute, 1983-1986 (Box 27, Folder 110)
  - Pocantico Planning Project - Final Report, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 111)
  - Plant Breeding Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 112)
  - President's Committee on the Arts and the Humanities, 1983-1986 (Box 27, Folder 113)
  - Princeton University, Department of History, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 114)
  - Roberts, Walter (University Corporation for Atmospheric Research), 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 115)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1977-1984 (Box 28, Folder 116)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center - Governing Council, 1982-1986 (Box 28, Folder 117)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center - Search File, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 118)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2025.
  - Winthrop Paul Rockefeller, 1973-1983 (Box 29, Folder 119)
  - Estate of Winthrop Rockefeller, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 120)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Trust and Estate, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 121)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Trust and Estate, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 122-123)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Trust and Estate, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 124)
  - JDR 3rd - Memos and Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 125)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller's Farmstead, Woodstock, VT, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 126)
  - NAR Memorial Resolution, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 127)
  - Memo to NAR - re: RBF Program, 1977 April 22 (Box 30, Folder 128)
  - NAR - Memos, 1974-1978 (Box 30, Folder 129)
  - NAR - Suggestions for Future Directions, 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 130)
  - Reports on RBF by Richard Parsons and Lindley Kimball, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 131)
  - David Rockefeller and David Rockefeller Office Memos, 1983-1987 (Box 31, Folder 132)
  - David Rockefeller Memos and Correspondence, 1978-1987 (Box 31, Folder 133)
  - RBF - Rockefeller Family Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 134)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller Memos and Correspondence, 1977-1987 (Box 32, Folder 135-136)
  - Dockets Currently Planned, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 137)
  - Deng, Francis M., 1987 (Box 32, Folder 138)
  - McCalpin, William F., 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 139)
  - Moody, Bill, 1983-1987 (Box 32, Folder 140)
  - O'Donnell, Kendra Stearns, 1981-1987 (Box 32, Folder 141)
  - Palmer, Hilary K., 1986 (Box 32, Folder 142)
  - Parsons, Richard, 1977-1987 (Box 32, Folder 143)
  - Phillips, Russell A., Jr., 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 144)
  - Shute, Benjamin R., Jr., 1980-1987 (Box 33, Folder 145)
  - Wahman, Thomas W., 1971-1987 (Box 34, Folder 146)
  - RBF - Committee - Audit, 1978-1986 (Box 34, Folder 147)
  - RBF - Committee - Creel, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 148)
  - RBF - Committee - Executive, 1980-1987 (Box 34, Folder 149)
  - RBF - Committee - Finance, 1981-1987 (Box 35, Folder 150)
  - RBF - Committee - Nominating, 1983-1987 (Box 35, Folder 151)
  - RBF - Committee - Review and Planning, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 152)
  - RBF - Committee - Planning, 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 153)
  - RBF - Investment Performance, 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 154)
  - RBF - Committee on Social Issues (LSR Chairman), 1980 (Box 36, Folder 155)
  - Trustee Letters re: The RBF, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 156)
  - Trustee Memos re: Economic, Governmental and Social Committees, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 157)
  - RBF - Trustees - Memos re: Meetings, 1977-1987 (Box 36, Folder 158)
  - Rockefeller Offices - Communication-Collaboration, 1985-1987 (Box 37, Folder 159)
  - RBF - Functional Expenses Budget, 1981-1986 (Box 37, Folder 160)
  - Office - Memoranda, 1975-1987 (Box 37, Folder 161)
  - Barney, Gerald O. - Global Studies Center, 1985-1987 (Box 37, Folder 162)
  - Barney, Gerald O., 1977-1984 (Box 38, Folder 163)
  - Zero Bond Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 164)
  - Connelly, Willard; Packard, Arthur W., 1936-1937 (Box 39, Folder 165)
  - Africa Trip - WMD, 1987 January (Box 39, Folder 166)
  - Africa Trip, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 167)
  - Trip to South Africa, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 168)
  - Trip to Far East, 1977 August-September (Box 39, Folder 169)
  - England-Stockholm Trip, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 170)
  - European Trip, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 171)
  - European Trip, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 172)
  - England Trip, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 173)
  - African-England Trip, 1974 May-June, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 174)
  - Trustee Nominations, 1972-1977 (Box 40, Folder 175)
  - JDR 3rd, 1973-1976 (Box 40, Folder 176)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 177)
  - David Rockefeller, 1973-1976 (Box 40, Folder 178)
  - Creel, Dana S., 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 179)
  - Snedcof, Harold, 1972-1974 (Box 40, Folder 180)
  - Walsh, Michaela L. (Box 40, Folder 181)
  - Program Overviews - International Program, National Program, New York City Program, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 182)
  - Real Estate Assets of the Voluntary Sector, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 183)
  - Royal Academy Trust - National Council, 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 184)
  - Royal Oak Foundation, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 185)
  - Sleepy Hollow Restorations, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 41, Folder 186-187)
  - Sleepy Hollow Restorations, Inc. - Board of Trustees, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 188)
  - Study of Solar and Renewable Energy (Box 42, Folder 189)
  - South Africa, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 190-191)
  - South Africa, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 192)
    - South Africa - "Witness to Apartheid", VHS (Box 2016:FA774:002)
  - South Africa Projects (Box 43, Folder 193-194)
  - South Africa Projects - Programme for Technological Careers (PROTEC), 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 195)
  - South Africa - Divestment, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 196)
  - Spears, Benzak, Salomon and Farrell, 1983-1986 (Box 44, Folder 197)
  - Strategic Metals Fund Limited, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 198)
  - Sunny Valley Foundation, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 199)
  - Synergos Institute, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 200)
  - U.S. Agricultural Development Corporation, 1982-1985 (Box 45, Folder 201)
  - U.S. Private Sector Support Group for Africa (United Nations), 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 202)
  - U.S. - Third World Discussion paper, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 203)
  - Vasser College - A-Z, 1979-1987 (Box 45, Folder 204)
  - University of Vermont - President's Council on Development, 1984-1987 (Box 46, Folder 205)
  - Volunteer Consulting Group, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 46, Folder 206)
  - WETA - Television 26-Radio FM 91, 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 207)
  - Wheeler, John, 1984-1986 (Box 47, Folder 208)
  - Wilson Center, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 209)
  - Winrock International, 1978, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 210-211)
  - Winrock International, 1978, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 212)
  - Winrock International - Development Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 213)
  - Winrock International - Finance Committee, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 214)
  - Winrock International - Investment Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 48, Folder 215)
  - Winrock International - Executive Committee, 1986 December 4 (Box 48, Folder 216)
  - WIIAD - Minutes of Meetings, 1984-1986 (Box 49, Folder 217)
  - Winrock International - Nominating Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 218)
  - Winrock International - Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 219)
  - Winrock International - Aspen-WYE Institute Visit, 1978 December 11 (Box 49, Folder 220)
  - Day File - Winrock International Institute fo Agricultural Development, 1984-1986 (Box 49, Folder 221)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 222)
  - Winrock - Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 50, Folder 223-225)
  - Winrock - Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 51, Folder 226-228)
  - Winrock Livestock and Training Center, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 229)
  - Winrock International Conference Center, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 230)
  - Winrock International - Williams, Ted Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 231)
  - Winrock - Roundtable Meetings (Box 52, Folder 232)
  - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Inc. - Board of Directors, 1974-1984 (Box 53, Folder 233)
  - Winrock - Board of Directors, 1977-1984 (Box 53, Folder 234)
  - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Inc., 1976 (Box 53, Folder 235)
  - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Inc. - IRS Ruling, 1975-1984 (Box 53, Folder 236)
  - Winrock - Executive Committee, 1977-1981 (Box 54, Folder 237)
  - Winrock - Finance Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 54, Folder 238)
  - Winrock - Financial Statements, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 239)
  - Winrock - Nominating Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 54, Folder 240)
  - Winrock - Investment Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 241)
  - Winrock - Personnel Committee, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 242)
  - Winrock - Plannning and Development Committee, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 243)
  - Winrock - Program Committee, 1979-1984 (Box 55, Folder 244)
  - Winrock International - Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 55, Folder 245)
  - Winrock International - Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 56, Folder 246-248)
  - Winrock International - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 249)
  - Winrock Merger, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 250-253)
  - Winrock-IADS-ADC Merger Plans, 1982-1984 (Box 58, Folder 254-257)
  - Candidates for CEO for Merged Winrock Organization, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 258)
  - Winrock International Dedication, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 259)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, 1975-1979, 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 260-262)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Archives - Background Material, 1976-1980 (Box 60, Folder 263)
  - Schnittker Evaluation Report, 1973-1978 (Box 60, Folder 264)
  - Winrock International Livestock and Training Center, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 265)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1979-1983 (Box 60, Folder 266)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1979-1983 (Box 61, Folder 267-270)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Estate - Automobile Museum, 1974-1976 (Box 61, Folder 271)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 272)
  - Winrock - David Rockefeller and Laurance S. Rockefeller Pledge Letters, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 273)
  - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - IRS Ruling, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 274)
  - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 275)
  - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - WILAD, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 276)
  - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - Press, 1984-1986 (Box 63, Folder 277)
  - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 278)
  - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 279)
  - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center - Exemption, Merger Petition, Certificate of Incorporation, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 280)
  - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 281)
  - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center - Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 282)
  - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center - Search Committee, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 283)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2024.
  - World Academy of Art and Science, 1983-1985 (Box 65, Folder 284)
  - World Council of Churches, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 285)
  - Wooster School, 1980-1984 (Box 66, Folder 286)
  - Wooster School - Trustees, 1978-1979 (Box 66, Folder 287)
  - Worldwatch Institute, 1984-1987 (Box 66, Folder 288)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Day File, 1986 January-June (Box 66, Folder 289)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Day File, 1986 July-September (Box 66, Folder 290)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Day File, 1986 October-December (Box 67, Folder 291)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Personal Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 67, Folder 292)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Personal Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 67, Folder 293)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Personal Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 294)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Personal - Employment (Box 67, Folder 295)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Personal - Princeton University, 1971-1979 (Box 67, Folder 296)
  - William M. Dietel (WMD) Personal - Semi-Personal Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 68, Folder 297-298)
  - Resumes - A-Z (Box 68, Folder 299-301)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Confidential material
  - Resumes - A-Z (Box 69, Folder 302-304)
  - Willam M. Dietel - Desk and Pocket Calendars, 1970-1985 (Box 70)